Guide to the Lewis L. Delafield, Eugene D. Hawkins and Affiliated Attorneys Records circa 1856-1921 (bulk, 1880s-1910) MS 157
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Boxes labeled H-D (Hawkins-Delafield), circa 1853-1924 (bulk 1880s-1910)
  - H-D Bundles #609, 675, circa 1900-1924 (Offsite-box 120)
    * Box numbered 609G held a loose pile of miscellaneous documents that seem to be handwritten working drafts. A few matters barely stand out: John G. Moore v. Sarah H. Aldrich et al (executors and trustees under will of Jane A. Moore), ca. 1892; Noyac Cottage Association matter, ca. 1890s; Meeks estate statement, ca. 1891; Louisville, New Albany & Chicago Railway Company agreement with Messrs. Poor and Greenough, 1891. Many more items, but rough drafts.
    * Estate of Georgiana Clinton O'Neal Barber, correspondence file (1918-1924) and financial records (1900-1921).
- Series IV. Numbered Pigeonhole Boxes, 1860s-1912 (bulk 1890s-1910)
  The series holds the content of numbered pigeonhole boxes in the collection. The overall content of the series has no particular coherence as all the firms in the collection are represented to some extent in this series, though primarily Hawkins and Delafield. Various Delafield and Hawkins family legal matters are here. More documents are found for Sailors Snug Harbor and Caleb Burbank matters.
  The series includes the content from 80 original boxes that were of "pigeonhole" size or slightly larger that were simply and distinctively numbered from 1 to 272, with many gaps. Many of the smaller original boxes were retained with their contents. Larger or deteriorated boxes, or boxes with few documents, were discarded and their contents transferred to plastic enclosures. Contents from the various boxes were not mixed together in any one plastic enclosure. The container list retains the sequencing of the boxes.
  - Pigeonhole box #1, circa 1893-1899 (Offsite-box 135)
    Appears to hold cases handled by Caleb Burbank:
    * Claus H. Stelling v. John A. Schilling et al, Kings County, ca. 1894.
    * Joseph C. Schrader v. John A. Schilling, Kings County, ca. 1894.
    * Reon Barnes v. Morris C. Mengis, ca. 1894.
    * Benjamin Cohen v. Thomas P. Kelly, Kings County, ca. 1894.
    * Maude B. Taudvin v. Union Central Life Insurance Company, ca. 1895.
    * Adelaide T. Willets v. Thomas Clapham and Georgia M. Clapham.
    * John P. Smith v. Hetta B. Patterson, et al, Kings County, ca. 1894.
    * Thomas C. Chappell v. Morris C. Mengis, ca. 1893.
    * Martin Reynolds v. William R. Baker, Kings County, ca. 1893.
    * Settlement of account of Valentine Loewer, executor of Anna Amalia Hosbach, ca. 1899.
    * Fred W. Elliott v. John H. Duke, et al, ca. 1899.
  - Pigeonhole box #4, circa 1891-1903 (Offsite-box 135)
    The box seems to hold both Caleb Burbank cases and those from the firm of Delafield, Gould and Longfellow:
    * Annie R. Lewis v. Charles A. Ricksecker et al, ca. 1903.
    * Settlement of account of Frederick L. Gilbert and Elizabeth M. Livingston as executors of Elizabeth M. Blague estate, ca. 1894.
    * Settlement of account of Maturin L. Delafield and Mary C. Delafield, guardians of Edward C. Delafield (infant), ca. 1899.
    * Matter of will of Lavinia A. Voris, ca. 1894.
    * George Thorpe v. Mary Miller, Johanna Schouler, et al, ca. 1895.
    * John P. Brooks v. Clara L. Radtke, Westchester County.
    * Henry McCready v. James Blackwood and Robert Douglas, ca. 1895.
    * Delia R. Ellis papers.
    * Fussell Ice Cream Company v. Braciforce L. Esten, ca. 1891.
    * City of Ironwood v. Thomas P. Wickes, ca. 1897.
    * Settlement of account of Grace L. Stevens Cooper, executrix of Mary A. Stevens estate, ca. 1897.
    * Rochester City and Brighton Rairoad Company bonds, ca. 1902.
    * Julius H. Preston et al v. "William" A. White et al, ca. 1902.
    * Ameen A. Shibley v. John B. Gendron, Rhode Island court, ca. 1900.
    * Estate of Schuyler Skaats, ca. 1895.
    * Walter T. Parker (firm of Burton & Parker) v. A. Willis Lightbourn, ca. 1893.
    * And various other matters, each with few documents.
  - Pigeonhole box #5, circa 1891-1902 (Offsite-box 136)
    Most, perhaps all, relates to Caleb Burbank cases:
    * Estate matters, especially taxation, re: Thomas Backus, ca. 1905.
    * Packet of railroad coupon bonds and insurance policies, ca. 1891.
    * Application of Caleb Burbank for commissions as notary public and other matters concerning various Burbanks.
    * Rhode Island National Bank v. Clara L. Radtke, Westchester County, ca. 1899.
    * Benjamin H. Irving (executor of Mary Irving estate) v. Jane R. Irving et al, ca. 1897.
    * Jones National Fence Company v. James F. Disken, ca. 1902.
    * Harriet E. Price v. Edward Price, ca. 1902.
    * Application of Arthur P. Quimby and Orville J. Quimby to sell real estate of Arthur, a minor, ca. 1898.
    * And many other unidentified matters, generally with few documents.
  - Pigeonhole boxes #7, 20, circa 1904-1910 (Offsite-box 136)
    Box 7 holds only one matter, that of the Ambrose B. Burbank will and possibly the later Newcomb v. Burbank dispute, ca. 1904-10.
    Box 20 holds:
    * Matter of Hatch, Keener, & Clute, firm dissolution, ca. 1905.
    * Newcomb, et al vs. Caleb Burbank, 1906-08.
    * Agreement between United Engineering and Contracting Company, Century Bank (trustee), General Electric Company, et al, ca. 1906.
  - Pigeonhole boxes #22, 24, 28, 29, 34, 37, 38, 40, circa 1899-1912 (Offsite-box 137)
    #22) Documents related to the will of Ambrose B. Burbank and the resulting lawsuit of David B. Newcomb, Mary E. Newcomb, and Georgiana Duvernois v. Caleb A. Burbank, executor of Ambrose B. Burbank will, circa 1890s-1910.
    #24) Correspondence with Florence K. Smith (in Ireland) and her attorney re: will (copy in the file) of her grandfather, Cyrus Knapp of Hackensack, NJ, ca. 1906.
    #28) Only one letter re: request of Hawkins-Delafield to collect a business claim from a London jeweler, 1905.
    #29) The bulk of the documents relate to Mary E. Gilroy (administratrix of Annie B. Gilroy estate) v. Andrew Mullen, Kings County, ca. 1902-08. There are a few documents re: an assignment from Mitchell Harrison, ca. 1899; and for James C. Colgate et al v. United States Leather Company et al, New Jersey courts, ca. 1907.
    #34) Retsof Mining Company matters, ca. 1907-12.
    #37) Print matter only re: Big Bonanza Mining Company of Latouche Island v. Agnes Robertson (executor of Andrew Robertson estate), et al; bill of complaint, U.S. District Court, Southern Dist of New York, 1909.
    #38) USA v. George W. Dally, ca. 1909. James Pereles et al v. H.A. Weil (US Marshal), Eastern District of Wisconsin. USA v. F.W. Keitl, et al, District Court for Colorado, ca. 1908. USA v. Edgar M. Biggs et al, District Court for Colorado. USA v. John I. Wells et al, District Court for Idaho, 1907. A few miscellaneous papers.
    #40) Primarily holds general reference material re: governing and incorporating a Delaware corporation. Relates to Pure Milk Company incorporation, ca. 1899.
  - Pigeonhole boxes #50, 52, 57, 68, 76, circa 1894-1909 (Offsite-box 138)
    #50) Settlement of account of Francis T. Garretson (executor of Charlotte W. Prime estate), ca. 1894. Application of Mary E. Williams (guardian of estate of Charles E. Williams (infant) for order directing county treasurer to pay certain funds, etc. Claims of Alfaro F. Perez of Frontera, Mexico (and E. Steiger) on the American Museum of Natural History, ca. 1902.
    #52) Carlton Strong v. George Greer et al, ca. 1902. Warner M. Leeds matters with Ida Gibson Whitney, ca. 1909, and other Leeds matters (only a few documents).
    #57) New Jersey Briquetting Company matters re: Mouquin, Offerman, & Wells Coal Company and re: Bressette & Wells, ca. 1904-06.
    #68) Eugene Hawkins personal papers, especially for property matters on East 67th Street at Park Avenue, ca. 1902-03.
    #76) David Newcomb et al v. Caleb Burbank et al, ca. 1909. John Wanamaker property matters, especially re: taxation of land on 4th Avenue impacted by rapid transit construction, ca. 1903.
  - Pigeonhole boxes #79, 80, 87, 91, circa 1892-1907 (Offsite-box 139)
    #79) Settlement of account of Edwin B. Meeks (executor of Joseph W. Meeks estate), with list of personal property of JW Meeks, ca. 1892.
    #80) People of the State of New York on the relation of George W. Perkins v. Edward Reardon (a peace officer) and Joseph F. Moss (a city magistrate), ca. 1906-07.
    #87) Application as to solvency of the United States Fidelity and Guaranty Company, ca. 1906-07.
    #91) Charles Hyde will/estate matters, Plainfield, NJ, ca. 1901. D.A. Clarkson matter re: property damage/claims at 279 Washington Street, New York City, caused by the Tarrant fire, ca. 1901. John H. Dunne v. Charles Henrotin, ca. 1899-1902.
  - Pigeonhole boxes #95, 102, 105, 108, 109, 113, circa 1901-1910 (Offsite-box 140)
    #95) Documents re: 62 East 67th Street at Park Avenue (Eugene Hawkins's mother, Sophia's, residence), including legal agreements, renovations (including correspondence with architects Snelling & Potter), etc., 1902-06.
    #102) Marion Sturgis v. Fifth Avenue Coach Company, ca 1907-08.
    #105) Association of the Bar of the City of New York, Committtee on Grievances complaint against attorney Henry A. Robinson, 1901. Also, a few other Bar Association-related documents, ca. 1908.
    #108) Mary Penniman and Gerald Hull Gray (trustees under will of John Knower) v. Mary Penniman (administratrix of John Knower estate) et al, ca. 1903.
    #109) William J. Cregan (trustee under deed by Jane A. McKenna to said William J. Cregan) v. Jane A. McKenna, Laura A. Cregan, and William Joseph Cregan, ca. 1908-10.
    #113) Application to reduce tax assessment of George Crocker on property in Tarrytown, New York, ca. 1907-10. Also includes perhaps related documents re: property in Greenburgh, Westchester County (agreement between Bainbridge S. Clark and Armedia S. Clark, ca. 1907).
  - Pigeonhole boxes #114, 115, 116, 118, circa 1906-1910 (Offsite-box 141)
    #114) Claims of Warner & Company against Anderson T. Herd and others, ca. 1908-10. Perhaps related documents re: agreement between Frederick Remsen and Henry W. Warner and Franklin M. Warner, 1909.
    #115) Brighton Yarn Company corporate matters (incorporation, capitalization, dissolution), ca. 1906-09.
    #116) James C. Colgate et al v. United States Leather Company et al, ca. 1907-09.
    #118) William J. Cregan (trustee under deed by Jane A. McKenna to said William J. Cregan) v. Jane A. McKenna, Laura A. Cregan, and William Joseph Cregan, ca. 1908-10.
  - Pigeonhole boxes #121, 126, 136, 138, circa 1860s-1910 (Offsite-box 142)
    #121) Settlement of account of Marshall Bell, executor of Fanny Hilton estate, 1904.
    #126) James C. Colgate matters re: lease etc. of property at 296-298 Madison Avenue, New York City, ca. 1907-09.
    #136) Application of Eugene D. Hawkins, as substituted trustee, for authority to sell certain real estate, notably 5 West 34th Street, New York City. This is a personal legal matter re: Sophia Hawkins (mother) and Dexter Hawkins estate, ca. 1860s-1901.
    #138) Matter of Sailors' Snug Harbor negotiations with John Wanamaker for lease of property in New York City, 1900-1901, 1909-10. Also a few Snug Harbor documents re: properties (ca. 1909) and Lewis L. Delafield's analysis of Captain Randall's will (1899).
  - Pigeonhole boxes #139, 142, 143, 144, 149, 157, circa 1895-1910 (Offsite-box 143)
    #139) City of New York v. Emily P. Delafield, 1908-09 (only a few documents).
    #142) Eugene Hawkins personal: Application by Sophia T. Hawkins for reduction of assessed value of 62 East 67th Street, ca. 1904. Some documents also re: 5 West 34th Street (Sophia), ca. 1899, and 51 East 67th Street (Eugene), ca. 1903.
    #143) Settlement of account of Jennie P. Childs as guardian of Paulding Fosdick (infant), ca. 1902.
    #144) Application of Louise Hartshorne Leeds for property tax refund, Nassau County, ca. 1906. Petition to have Mary Hopkins adjudged bankrupt, U.S. District Court, Southern Dist of New York, ca. 1899.
    #149) Jennie T. Hagen (executor of Gertrude P. Winston estate) v. Sweetser, Pembrook & Company, William N. Kremer, et al, ca. 1907-10.
    #157) Settlement of account of Alida Jacques (executrix of William S. Jacques estate), Kings County, ca. 1895-1904. There are also some documents re: matter of solvency of National Surety Company, 1907.
  - Pigeonhole boxes #159, 160, 163, 164, 170, 172, circa 1897-1909 (Offsite-box 144)
    #159) Settlement of account of Elizabeth J. Dana and Fifth Avenue Trust Company (administrators of Anderson Carroll Dana estate), ca. 1907-08.
    #160) Application of Samuel Levin for citizenship (only a few documents), ca. 1908.
    #163) Max Blumenthal v. The W.H. Purcell Company, ca. 1897, re: failure to pay for delivery of bushels of malt to the Bavarian Star Brewing Company.
    #164) Last wills & testaments of George W. Perkins and Evalina B. Perkins, 1909.
    #170) Ida B. Forbes (administratrix of Joseph H. Batty estate) v. American Museum of Natural History, ca. 1907-08, in re: 1902-06 agreements with Batty to collect birds and mammals in Central America.
    #172) Claim of Louise Van Winklee on Henry Marquand & Co., ca. 1902, re: payment on bond.
  - Pigeonhole boxes #179, 187, 189, 195, 200, 204, circa 1903-1910 (Offsite-box 145)
    #179) Deed of trust between Louise Hartshorne Leeds and William Jay Schieffelin, William H. Holtzclaw re: creating a fund in support of the Utica Mississippi Normal & Industrial Institute [African-American schooling], ca. 1909.
    #187) Charles P. Curtiss v. Sweetser, Pembrook & Company, George H. Franklin, et al, ca. 1907-10.
    #189) William J. Hart and George W. Plunkitt v. Morris K. Jessup (as president of the American Museum of Natural History), ca. 1907.
    #195) Trustees of the Reformed Protestant Dutch Church of Mott Haven v. Interborough Rapid Transit Commission and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1906, 1909. Agreements between Horace Hamilton Brashier, Nellie Barber (Salvage) Brashier and New York Security & Trust Company, including a marriage settlement, ca. 1903.
    #200) 2 print matter items: tariff legislation and a clipping.
    #204) Sarah Lincoln v. Sweetser, Pembrook & Company, George W. Perkins, George H. Franklin, et al, ca. 1907-10.
  - Pigeonhole boxes #205, 208, 211, 214, 215, 217, circa 1895-1909 (Offsite-box 146)
    #205) Trustees of the Sailors' Snug Harbor in the City of New York v. George Sutherland, ca. 1907-09.
    #208) Theresa Klauber v. Manhattan Railway Company and Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company, ca. 1898-1902.
    #211) Henry L. Kreusler v. Willet Realty Company et al, ca. 1906.
    #214) James B. Ludlow v. Annie Ludlow Winters and others, and Edgar J. Shipman (administrator of Julietta Truslow estate), Westchester County, ca. 1895-1908.
    #215) Trustees of the Sailors' Snug Harbor in the City of New York v. Charles Jackson, action #1, ca. 1909.
    #217) Trustees of the Sailors' Snug Harbor in the City of New York v. Charles Jackson and Dumont Clarke (executors of William B. Dinsmore estate), action #2, ca. 1909.
  - Pigeonhole boxes #220, 222, 226, 234, 236, 237, circa 1894-1909 (Offsite-box 147)
    #220) Trustees of the Sailors' Snug Harbor in the City of New York v. Theodore Wolters and William Ulmer Brewery, ca. 1908-09.
    #222) Jeanne Symen (whose professional name or title is "La Juanita") v. Kester Bial and Company, U.S. District Court, Southern Dist of New York, ca. 1894-1900.
    #226) Application of majority of directors of the Bavarian Star Brewing Company for a voluntary dissolution, ca. 1897-98, and related matters concerning the Colonial Brewery, Fox Brothers & Co., and Max Blumenthal.
    #234) Emily P. Delafield (died 1909) will and estate matters (mother of Frederick P. and Lewis L. Delafield.
    #236) Earl A. Smith (administrator of Andrew J. Smith estate) v. American Museum of Natural History, Otsego County, re: suit over injury, ca. 1902-07.
    #237) Smith v. Charles A. Baldwin, re: business contract dispute, ca. 1899.
  - Pigeonhole boxes #238, 239, 243, 245, 247, 248, circa 1895-1909 (Offsite-box 148)
    #238) Frederic R. Coudert (trustee substituted for Louise Pelletier) v. Caroline Huerstel et al, ca. 1895-1901. Samuel T. Hubbard et al v. Edmond Huerstel, ca. 1899.
    #239) A few letters re: the Unitarian Association and the Church of the Messiah apparently re: rapid transit construction/blasting along Park Avenue, ca. 1901.
    #243) John J. McDermott (receiver of property of Abraham Rosenthal) v. Charles Rosenthal and Abraham Rosenthal. Also, McDermott v. Clara Rosenthal and other related matters. Ca. 1908-09.
    #245) Robert J. McKean v. William F. Johnston (executor of James McKean estate), ca. 1902-03.
    #247) John Delafield estate matters (Richard Delafield, administrator), ca. 1899-1902. Also has copies of some documents re: John Barker Church estate.
    #248) King Bridge Company v. Amsterdam Construction Company and Fidelity & Deposit Company of Maryland, ca. 1900-02.
  - Pigeonhole boxes #249, 250, 253, 256, 257, 259, circa 1891-1909 (Offsite-box 149)
    #249) Various matters, several related in some way: William H. Daily and Pacific Coast Smelting and Refining Company v. Christopher Furness, John F. Hately, Frank P. Deering, and The Copper King, Ltd; Copper King Ltd bankruptcy; Crocker-Woolworth National Bank of San Francisco v. William H. Daily, Pacific Coast Smelting and Refining Company, Edward K. Jones, Washington Gregg, et al, all California courts, ca. 1903-06. Also: Printed copy of will of Nathaniel P. Bailey, 1891; and Maria Tillou Kemble v. Leon Durand Bonnet, ca. 1908.
    #250) Elizabeth Duval Littell v. Leon Durand Bonnet, re: Bonnet bankruptcy, ca. 1908-09.
    #253) Charles Byers v. Theodore H. Price, William G. McCormick, Ralph M. Stuart Wortley, Berhard J. Harrison and George Crocker et al (firm of Price, McCormick & Co.). Also suits by Samuel T. Davis Jr. and by Mark Harris v. Price, McCormick & Co. All ca. 1897-1901.
    #256) Mrs. Anna E. Marks v. Germania Savings Bank and related subpoena issued by Caleb Burbank as a Commissioner to take depositions, ca. 1898-1901.
    #257) Settlement of account of Isaac S. Mack, administrator of Eleonora Mack estate, ca. 1903.
    #259) A very few documents re: estate of J.J. Moore re: application to reduce property valuation, Queens County.
  - Pigeonhole boxes #268, 272, circa 1900-1908 (Offsite-box 150)
    #268) Holds only 1 document: a legal analysis "The right to the use of a family name by a person not a member of that family" by W.H.G., 1908.
    #272) Application of Jennie P. Childs as administratrix of Charles B. Fosdick estate for damage award in connection with the opening of Webster Avenue from Mosholu Parkway to Bronx River Road, ca. 1900-02.
- Series V. Contents of boxes with various labeling, 1850s-1921 (bulk, 1880s-1910)
  The series includes the content of about 60 boxes that had a variety of miscellaneous labelings, ambiguous labels, misleading labels, incomplete labels, or no labels. Consequently, there is no particular arrangement to this series. The container list is presented simply as an inventory of the content of each N-YHS record carton. Where original boxes were retained, that is noted. As with the other series, content of boxes not retained were transfered to plastic enclosures; content from various boxes was not mixed together in any one plastic enclosure.
  As with Series IV, this series holds content that represents all of the lawyers in the collection. Many of the files relate to the law office administration of Delafield and Longfellow, as well as personal papers of Bejamin Gould and of Longfellow, such as those concerning his property in Roque Bluffs, Maine. A notable document is the letterpress copybook of Dexter Hawkins for 1856-58. There is substantial documentation for a breach of contract matter: Samuel R. Smith v. Frank E. Anderson. Additional documents are found for matters seen in other series, including Trustees of the Sailors' Snug Harbor in the City of New York; Sarah May Le Brantz v. William G. Conklin; Wilhelm Pickhardt; securities matters; and more.
  - N-YHS Box 101, 1900-1907 (Offsite-box 101)
    This box holds various matters:
    * Joseph J. Cunneely et al v. New York Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1901.
    * City of New York v. Marion S. Sturgis, ca. 1905-07. Also Marion Sturgis v. Fifth Avenue Coach Company.
    * Matilda W. White v. Cortlandt F. Bishop, trustees of the Sailors' Snug Harbor in the City of New York, et al, ca. 1903.
    * Herman B. Inches will, 1900.
    * Eustis L. Hopkins (executor of Albert G. Hyde estate, and trustee for Helen M. Valentine) v. Seymour J. Hyde, et al, ca. 1904.
  - N-YHS Box 116, circa 1903-1908 (Offsite-box 116)
    * Marion Sturgis v. Fifth Avenue Coach Company, ca. 1904.
    * Settlement of accounts of Edwin B. Meeks, administrator of Joseph W. Meeks estate, Suffolk County, ca. 1906-08.
    * Wilding Blackburn v. Solomon W. Johnson as president of American News Company, ca. 1903-04 (Caleb Burbank, attorney)
  - N-YHS Box 120, circa 1896-1910 (Offsite-box 120)
    Mostly Robert Sturgis matters:
    * Settlement of accounts of W.R. & T.G. Patten, executors of Thomas Patten and administrators of will of Jane Adelaide Woodruff, ca. 1896.
    * Michael Greenberg v. Esther D. Greenberg, ca. 1898.
    * Application of Lilian Oliver Shiff and Eva Madeline Shiff (infants undr 14) to sell real estate, ca. 1899.
    * Lucy Chauncey will, ca. 1899.
    * William Austin matter, ca. 1899.
    * Joseph D. Livingston v. Joseph J. Byers.
    * Edmund Menard v. W.D. Willis et al, ca. 1910.
  - N-YHS Box 121, circa 1880s-1910 (Offsite-box 121)
    * John Galt Smith will and estate matters, including re: his wife Elizabeth Shipley Smith, executrix and guardian of George Kennedy Smith, ca. 1892-1902.
    * Fussell Ice Cream Company v. Eugene A. Furber and Emma Furber, ca. 1895, and other actions by Fussell against others.
    * Charles Stone v. Edward H. Horner, ca. 1890-91.
    * Morris C. Mengis v. Robert H. Bohm, ca. 1894.
    * Oscar M. Draper v. Albert Eddy, ca. 1897.
    * Trustees of the Peabody Education Fund v. Charles H. Jenkins et al, ca. 1894.
    * Ida S. Park v. Peterson Company, ca. 1898.
    * Jennie Carr v. Jane Seville, ca. 1880s.
    * Union Trust Company of New York v. Hamilton Park Company et al, ca. 1898.
    * Trustees of the Sailors Snug Harbor in the City of New York v. Samuel I. Hyman et al.
    * Joy, Langdon & Company matter, ca. 1909-10.
    * And a few other matters, all Caleb Burbank cases.
  - N-YHS Box 122, circa 1900-1906 (Offsite-box 122)
    Delafield & Longfellow matters: Various Indiana matters concerning Elkhart Electric Company, Home Electric Light & Power Company, Elkhart Paper Company, etc. The bankers Thompson, Tenney & Crawford are also involved with these. Circa 1900-03. Also re: Chicago & Alton Equipment Association and railroad equipment bonds, ca. 1904-06.
  - N-YHS Box 127, circa 1902-1909 (Offsite-box 127)
    This entire box holds Sarah May Le Brantz v. William G. Conklin (executor of Sarah Ann Waters estate), et al, and the related, earlier matter re: Sarah Ann Waters (alleged incompetent person) v. William G. Conklin, ca. 1902-09. This continues into the following box 128.
  - N-YHS Box 128, circa 1893-1909 (Offsite-box 128)
    Much of this box continues, from above box 127, Sarah May Le Brantz v. William G. Conklin (executor of Sarah Ann Waters estate), et al, and the related, earlier matter re: Sarah Ann Waters (alleged incompetent person) v. William G. Conklin, ca. 1902-09.
    The box also holds:
    * Auto-Electric Company matters, ca. 1900.